import { Quiz } from '../Types/types'

const quizzes: Quiz[] = [
  {
    id: '1',
    name: 'Quiz 1',
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'quiz one question 1',
        answer: 'quiz one answer 1',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'quiz one question 2',
        answer: 'quiz one answer 2',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'quiz one question 3',
        answer: 'quiz one answer 3',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'quiz one question 4',
        answer: 'quiz one answer 4',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'quiz one question 5',
        answer: 'quiz one answer 5',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '2',
    name: 'Quiz 2',
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'quiz two question 1',
        answer: 'quiz two answer 1',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'quiz two question 2',
        answer: 'quiz two answer 2',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'quiz two question 3',
        answer: 'quiz two answer 3',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'quiz two question 4',
        answer: 'quiz two answer 4',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'quiz two question 5',
        answer: 'quiz two answer 5',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '3',
    name: 'Quiz 3',
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'quiz three question 1',
        answer: 'quiz three answer 1',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'quiz three question 2',
        answer: 'quiz three answer 2',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'quiz three question 3',
        answer: 'quiz three answer 3',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'quiz three question 4',
        answer: 'quiz three answer 4',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'quiz three question 5',
        answer: 'quiz three answer 5',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '4',
    name: 'Quiz 4',
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'quiz four question 1',
        answer: 'quiz four answer 1',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'quiz four question 2',
        answer: 'quiz four answer 2',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'quiz four question 3',
        answer: 'quiz four answer 3',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'quiz four question 4',
        answer: 'quiz four answer 4',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'quiz four question 5',
        answer: 'quiz four answer 5',
      },
    ],
  },
]

export default quizzes
